question_data = [
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Matt Damon played an astronaut stranded on an extraterrestrial planet in both of the movies "
                    "Interstellar and The Martian.",
        "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "To bypass US Munitions Export Laws, the creator of the PGP published all the source code in book "
                 "form. ",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "United States President John F. Kennedy was assassinated during his presidential motorcade in "
                 "Atlanta, Georgia on November 22nd, 1963.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the game Dead by Daylight, the killer Michael Myers is refered to as &quot;The Shape&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Kiznaiver is an adaptation of a manga.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In &quot;Doctor Who&quot;, the Doctor gets his TARDIS by stealing it.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "L&#039;H&ocirc;pital was the mathematician who created the "
                 "homonymous rule that uses derivatives to evaluate limits with "
                 "indeterminations.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Hidden in the files for &quot;Mario Kart Arcade GP&quot; is a picture of the Beslan school hostage "
                 "crisis.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "YouTube personality Jenna Marbles served as an executive producer of the film Maximum Ride (2016).",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The mitochondria is the powerhouse of the cell.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
